topgamesfree.net 2013-06-06

# Privacy Policy | Top Games Free

## General Policy.

The games provided by this site are considered to be from the public domain, e.g. they are widely found on many other gaming sites etc., and comply with second party site’s policies. We try our best to give as much credit back to those authors/owners/organisations etc. as possible.

But if you believe such a game should not be featured on our website, Please contact us at webmaster@Topgamesfree.net and we shall arrange to take off the game as soon as possible. Usually within 24-48 hours.”

## Multi-Player Games Policy.

• All visitors may enter and play multiplayer games at their own risk.  
• Topgamesfree.net is not responsible for any vulgar or offensive language, or anything that may offend anyone in general.  
• Anyone offended with offensive language or inappropriate material should not enter a chat room – that includes our Multi-Player chat rooms as well.  
• Anyone caught causing offense in our chat rooms will be immediately deleted from our user database.  
• If you see or witness anyone causing offense in our chat rooms, please inform us and provide us with some kind of evidence (e.g. a snapshot of the screen containing the chat window).

## Your Privacy

Your privacy is important to us. To better protect your privacy we provide this notice explaining our online information practices and the choices you can make about the way your information is collected and used. To make this notice easy to find, we make it available on our homepage and at every point where personally identifiable information may be requested.

## Log Files

Like many other Web sites, Topgamesfree.net makes use of log files. The information inside the log files includes internet protocol ( IP ) addresses, type of browser, Internet Service Provider ( ISP ), date/time stamp, referring/exit pages, and number of clicks to analyze trends, administer the site, track user’s movement around the site, and gather demographic information. IP addresses, and other such information are not linked to any information that is personally identifiable.

## Cookies and Web Beacons

Topgamesfree.net does use cookies to store information about visitors preferences, record user-specific information on which pages the user access or visit, customize Web page content based on visitors browser type or other information that the visitor sends via their browser.

## DoubleClick DART Cookie

Google, as a third party advertisement vendor, uses cookies to serve ads on this site. The use of DART cookies by Google enables them to serve adverts to visitors that are based on their visits to this website as well as other sites on the internet.  
To opt out of the DART cookies you may visit the Google ad and content network privacy policy at the following url http://www.google.com/privacy_ads.html Tracking of users through the DART cookie mechanisms are subject to Google’s own privacy policies.  
Other Third Party ad servers or ad networks may also use cookies to track users activities on this website to measure advertisement effectiveness and other reasons that will be provided in their own privacy policies, Topgamesfree.net has no access or control over these cookies that may be used by third party advertisers.  
Some of our advertising partners may use cookies and web beacons on our site. Our advertising partners include, Google Adsense, CPMStar, EpicGameAds, Game Advertising Online, Value Click Media.  
These third-party ad servers or ad networks use technology to the advertisements and links that appear on Topgamesfree.net send directly to your browsers. They automatically receive your IP address when this occurs. Other technologies ( such as cookies, JavaScript, or Web Beacons ) may also be used by the third-party ad networks to measure the effectiveness of their advertisements and / or to personalize the advertising content that you see. Topgamesfree.net has no access to or control over these cookies that are used by third-party advertisers.  
You should consult the respective privacy policies of these third-party ad servers for more detailed information on their practices as well as for instructions about how to opt-out of certain practices. Topgamesfree.net’s privacy policy does not apply to, and we cannot control the activities of, such other advertisers or web sites.  
If you wish to disable cookies, you may do so through your individual browser options. More detailed information about cookie management with specific web browsers can be found at the browsers’ respective websites.

## Our Commitment To Childrens Privacy

Protecting the privacy of the very young is especially important. For that reason, Topgamesfree.net will never collect or maintain information at our website from those we actually know are under 13, and no part of our website is structured to attract anyone under 13.  
Under our Terms of Service, children under 13 are not allowed to access our service.

## Links to third party Websites

We have included links on this site for your use and reference. We are not responsible for the privacy policies on these websites. You should be aware that the privacy policies of these sites may differ from our own.

## Changes to this Privacy Statement

The contents of this statement may be altered at any time, at our discretion.  
If you require any more information or have any questions about our privacy policy, please feel free to contact us by email at admin@topgamesfree.net.
